https://www.ekw.mt/privacy

E-Catalogue
Corporate WearCorporateKnitwearShirts & BlousesSuits & FormalWomen's FashionHospitality & HealthAprons & ServiceHealth & BeautyWinter WearHoodiesJackets & CoatsSweatpantsSweatshirtsCollectionsBrave Soul FashionDenimFitted CollectionSports & LeisurePerformancePolosSweatersT-shirtsPolos & CasualPolos & CasualT-shirts & VestsKidsMen'sOrganicWomen'sShirts & BlousesFitted CollectionMen'sWomen'sTrousers & ShortsChinosFitted CollectionFormalWorkwearWorkwear & Safety WearFleeceHigh VisibilityPolosSafetywearKids & SchoolwearInfants & ToddlersFootwearMen'sSocksWomen'sWorkHeadwearBags & LuggageShoppingSport & LeisureTravelMarketing, Home & LivingHome & LivingWinter EssentialsOrganic
Custom MadeEmbroiderySchool Uniforms
Privacy Policy
Please read the following terms and conditions. In using this website, you agree to these terms and conditions of use.
This web site is operated by EagleK-Wear Ltd, Notabile Road, Mriehel, Malta. Tel: +356 21442329. If you have any queries about this web site, please contact us at the above address or email info@eaglek-wear.com
Privacy and Cookies
Most websites use cookies in order to improve the user experience by enabling that website to 'remember' you, either for the duration of your visit using a 'session cookie' or for repeat visits using a 'persistent cookie'. Cookies are small data files that are used as unique identifiers. They are sent from the website's servers to your computer or mobile phone and stored on your device, and may then be sent back to our website's servers with updated data as you browse the website.Cookies are used to record information about your preferences as you browse our website, which allows us to improve your experience by tailoring the website accordingly. Cookies can also be used to identify you every time you revisit our website. A session cookie will expire at the end of your browsing session once you close your web browser. Persistent cookies on the other hand have a set expiry date and will be stored on your computer until either this date is reached, or you delete your cookies using your browser settings.
This site uses some or all of the following cookies:
1. Session Cookie
This website may use a session cookie to maintain information about each visit to the website and enable core site functionality. This cookie does not contain any personal information, and only lasts for the duration of your visit, being deleted as soon as you close your web browser.
2. Load Balancer CookieThis cookie is essential to help ensure that the website loads efficiently by distributing visits across multiple web servers. This cookie does not contain any personal information, and only lasts for the duration of your visit, being deleted as soon as you close your web browser.
3. Google AnalyticsThis cookie allows us to count page visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site using a service provided by Google Analytics. We also implement Google Demographics and Interest Reporting to better understand the browsing habits, interests and demographics of our vistors. For more information about Google's privacy policy, please see www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings, see https://www.google.com/settings/ads. Additionally vistors may wish to use the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on found at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/  If you don't want to receive cookies, it is possible to modify your browser so that it notifies you when cookies are sent to it, or you can refuse cookies altogether. You can also delete cookies that have already been set.If you wish to restrict or block web browser cookies which are set on your device, you can do this through your browser settings (the help function within your browser should tell you how). Alternatively, you may wish to visit www.aboutcookies.org which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of desktop browsers.By continuing to use this website without making any such modifications to your browser, we will assume an implied acceptance of their use.
Data protection, privacy, storing and sharing information
Information from our customers enables us to continually improve the service we offer. However, we take privacy of information relating to our customers very seriously and comply with all Malta data protection laws in collecting, storing and using this information. Using this Web Site, or when contacting us both on-line and over the telephone, may involve you giving us certain information about yourself or your business, including your name and address, telephone number and email address. Any information we receive from you, will be stored by us and we will take all reasonable care to keep your personal data secure and to prevent any unauthorised access to it. We may use this information to contact you by email, telephone or post to provide you with details about our services, about employment opportunities with us or any other information which we believe may be of interest to you. It is intended that by providing information about yourself to us you consent to their use for the above purposes. Other than as required by law or in the prevention of fraud, we will not pass information we hold about you to any other organisation. If you do not want us to use this information in this way please contact us at info@eaglek-wear.com
Use of this website
This website contains material which is owned by EagleK-Wear Ltd. or its suppliers. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. It is protected by intellectual property laws including, but not limited to, copyright. You may download, view, copy and print information and documentation held at this website provided that the materials are used solely for your own personal use or for product / supplier research in connection with your business or your employer's business. Commercial use is not permitted. The materials may not be altered or modified in any way.
Professional advice
Information provided on pages held at this site and in any documents downloaded from this site is provided for general information only. It is subject to change without notice. EagleK-Wear Ltd is not responsible for any inaccuracies, makes no representation and gives no warranty as to its accuracy. Since the information was not prepared for you personally, it is not intended to form recommendations or advice. It is your sole responsibility to satisfy yourself that the information is suitable for your purposes. Nothing on this website is intended to be nor should be construed as an offer to enter into a contractual relationship.
Trademarks
Your use of this site and any materials downloaded, viewed, copied or printed does not authorise you to use any names or trademarks of EagleK-Wear Ltd, its trading partners or associates and no links without consent.
Links to other sites
EagleK-Wear Ltd cannot be held liable for any material or representations contained in other websites, nor does EagleK-Wear Ltd endorse or make representations in respect to such websites. All links are used at your own risk. In evoking links to other sites, you agree to accept these conditions of use. You may not create a link to this website from another website or document without EagleK-Wear Ltd’s prior written consent.
Virus infection
EagleK-Wear Ltd takes all-reasonable precautions to prevent virus infection of files contained on this site but cannot guarantee such prevention therefore we accept no liability for viruses. It is recommended that you take all appropriate measures and precautions to ensure appropriate safeguards are in place before downloading information. In using this site you also agree to take all appropriate measures and precautions to prevent the introduction of viruses by you to files held at this website.
Exclusion and limitation of liability
EagleK-Wear Ltd shall be under no liability to you whatsoever whether in contract, tort or otherwise for any direct, indirect or consequential loss or damages whatsoever including without limitation; loss of contracts, profits, anticipated savings, revenue, business, data, stoppage to other work or direct howsoever arising, due to your use of or in connection with this website. The material and information provided on this web site are provided without any warranties and implied terms and conditions are excluded.
Law
The Laws of Malta govern these terms and conditions and you agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Maltese Courts.
Eagle K-Wear Co.Ltd.
Notabile Road,
